But we are not finished here and another
Point exists and another use case exists that I want to go through so I closed this one and I come back to yes
I click leave and I come back to
Fotour homepage
So the next thing that I want to do in Fotour is
Headshot right so what is headshot when it comes to headshot for example, let's say that you have
Taken a photo out of your let's say head or out of your upper body or something like that
And then you want to convert it to a certain kind of
Look, you know a certain kind of professional look so you can use it as your profile as your
LinkedIn profile, you know or in your resume or something like that